X

Abhinav Bhowmik

Student

Motivated Internship Student working toward BCA degree. Hardworking and resourceful individual commended for first-rate collaboration, organizational and time management abilities. Committed to developing career path and expanding work experience. Strong knowledge of coding languages like Java and Python and also proficient in web development elements Javascript, Node. js and Express.

Work History

2020-12 - Internship Student

2020-12 TutoRaj, Work from Home

- Engaged with customers to effectively build rapport and lasting relationships.
- Helped customers locate products and checked store system for merchandise at other sites.
- Boosted sales by conferring with customers to evaluate purchase requirements and recommend best-fit company offerings.

2020-12 - Internship Student

Team Everest, Work from home

- Prepared and submitted professional proposals to select publishers to outline works, promotional skills and literary experience.
- Produced original, creative content for promotional advertisements and marketing materials.

Education

2020-12

High School Diploma

Lucknow Public School - Kanpur Road Ashiyana, Sector I, Lucknow

2020-07 - BCA

Current The Heritage Academy - Chowbaga Rd, Mundapara,

Chak Kolarkhal, West Bengal

Certifications

2021-09 The Web Developer Bootcamp Online Course by Colt

Steele

Hobbies:

Coding, Football and Chess

Contact

Address

Kolkata, West Bengal, 700148

Phone

8240635450

E-mail

bhowmikabhinav@gmail.co

m

Skills

Python

Excellent

Java

•••••

Excellent

HTML, CSS

••••

Very Good

Javasc -ript Very Good

Node.js

••••

Very Good

Microsoft Word , Powerpoint , Excel

xcel

Very Good

Languages

Hindi

••••• Excellent

Bengali

••••

Very Good

English

Fuellant

Excellent